As for Twilight's mission next week…
WISE - SAFE HOUSE G
In order to take every precaution,
we have decided to go as planned
and make this a joint operation with you.
Please work hard.
Understood.
Fiona Frost is an office worker
at Berlint General Hospital.
The woman is a spy working for WISE.
Please relay the information to Twilight.
Work out the plans together.
Roger.
Please be careful not to get in the way
of Operation Strix.
How is Operation Strix coming along?
There's slow progress.
But we always knew that this was
a long-term operation.
I apologize.
If only I was available
when the plan was set in motion.
Then I could have supported him
by playing the role of his wife.
In fact, it's not too late to use me.
Eden Academy will become suspicious
if he keeps getting new wives.
Sometimes it's more convenient
to use the locals.
We're keeping the Forger family as is.
You should just concentrate
on your mission.
What if Mrs. Forger quits her role?
Then there would be no other choice.
Huh? Stop plotting things
that will come to no good.
Excuse me.
Hey!
-How scary.
-Did you hear that?
She wants to take credit for
Twilight's work in order to get promoted.
She's capable of backstabbing
her own ally.
Many called her "She-devil,"
"cold-blooded," and "brazen."
She remains stone-faced
as she pursues her mission,
so others feel uneasy around her.
Her codename is Nightfall.
The woman was harboring an ambition.
MISSION 21: NIGHTFALL
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
Today's breakfast was another failure.
And Loid ended up making lunch.
I want to hurry up and learn to make
something other than stew.
Who could it be?
Coming.
Um…
May I ask who you are?
Excuse me. I'm Dr. Forger's colleague
at work.
My name is Fiona Frost.
Loid's colleague?
I'm sorry.
My husband is out walking the dog
with my daughter.
I see.
I already knew that he was out.
Your daughter left this behind
the other day when she came to visit.
So, I came to return it.
I see.
Thank you so much.
Since you're here,
would you like to come in
and wait for them?
I think I'll take you up on that offer.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Wow. She's so beautiful.
-What is it?
-Nothing at all!
This is a lovely home.
Does she think that I'm his mistress?
The truth is, I'm ready to take her place
as his wife at moment's notice.
So, she's not entirely wrong.
My husband chose all of the furniture…
Yor Briar.
I will get rid of you if you become
a hindrance to Operation Strix.
But this woman…
has her guard up.
She's our first guest aside from
Yuri and Franky.
I'm so nervous.
I'm a wife. I'm a wife.
Nonetheless, it's too risky
for me to forcibly remove her.
It's better to make her leave this family
of her own will.
Your daughter, Anya,
seems like she's a very active girl.
Yes. Anya is always full of energy.
I'm sure it must be very difficult.
Isn't child-rearing exhausting?
After all, she's nothing
but a stepdaughter to you.
Don't try too hard and unburden yourself.
Difficult? Why?
Being energetic is a very good thing.
I wouldn't know what to do
if she wasn't energetic,
but I have so much fun being with Anya.
She's acting as if she's her real mother.
But,
Loid takes on many roles,
so he always seems to be so busy.
It's all because I'm so incompetent.
That's right. You should realize
just how inexperienced you are.
You're not fit for this role.
Oh, that's right. Doctor Forger
is always grumbling at work saying,
"My wife is always…"
Anya's home!
Welcome home.
Fiona. Why are you here?
Hello, Doctor.
He came back earlier than I expected.
She came to return something
that Anya left behind.
Anya's magnifying glass!
I see. Thank you.
She came all the way here for that?
Is there an urgent matter?
You came back early.
It looked like it was going to rain soon,
so we came home early.
You didn't have to come all the way here.
WHAT IS IT, AGENT NIGHTFALL?
It's okay, since I was shopping nearby.
I JUST WANTED TO ASSESS
THE MAIN SITE OF OPERATION STRIX
Th… this lady is a spy too!
Oh, that supermarket on Second Avenue?
ASSESS? ASSESS WHAT?
What is she doing?
Agents should be avoiding
unnecessary contact with each other.
The onions were on sale.
TWILIGHT, IS WALKING THE DOG
IMPERATIVE TO THIS OPERATION?
Is that so?
Maybe I should go buy some too.
Pumpkins and pasta were on sale too.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE MAKING THIS WOMAN
DO THOSE MENIAL TASKS?
But the register was very crowded.
IS SHE NOT COOPERATIVE?
That store has the best shrimp.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY…?
I forgot to mention this to you before,
TWILIGHT, IT IS A LOSS FOR THE WORLD
but I'm allergic to shrimp.
IF SOMEONE LIKE YOU
IS WASTING YOUR TALENT ON PLAYING HOUSE
I PROPOSE TO RE-EVALUATE THIS PLAN
THIS IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS
This lady doesn't get along with Father?
Is she an evil spy?
Her face looks scary too.
Twilight, I love you.
Huh?
I love…
you!
I LOVE YOU
-This is delicious, Nightfall!
-I'm so glad!
You can do laundry and you're
a great cook! You're so amazing!
Oh, please.
Twilight, this is how much I earned
this month. Please use it as you like.
Nightfall, you're so…
To help out your next mission,
I researched everything about the enemies
from their names, age, weapon of choice
and all the other minor details.
Amazing! You're so amazing, Nightfall!
You're so perfect!
I don't need that clumsy woman anymore.
I'll marry you, Nightfall,
in order to attain world peace.
Even if our mission doesn't call for it,
I will give you my all.
Her codename is Nightfall. Her ambition
was to become Twilight's wife.
I'm a much better fit to play the role
of his wife!
I'll prove that I can provide both
domestic and operational support!
For our honeymoon,
we would go to the tropical islands…
What is she thinking?
Loid, I'll make some coffee.
Anya, do you want hot chocolate?
Anya?
Doctor Forger is always grumbling at work
saying, "My wife is always…"
She's always so clumsy and useless.
Should I report her to the authorities?
Fiona, do you want to be my new wife?
Oh, are you serious?
Then I'll visit you at home soon.
But…
with the way I am,
I can't blame him for feeling that way.
I can't even make a simple breakfast.
-Here you go.
-Hot chocolate!
Here's the milk.
Thanks, Yor.
Twilight likes his coffee black.
Not even once have I ever seen him
drink coffee with milk.
You didn't even know that,
and you're playing the role of his wife?
Let me take over.
That can't be! Did his sense of taste
change after he became a family man?
There's a side of Twilight
that I don't know about?
A side that he only shows her?
No. He's just playing
the role of Loid Forger.
He's playing the role of
someone who adds milk.
He's adapting himself to this household.
Just as I expected of you. I love you.
I have to add milk to reduce
the damage to my stomach.
In fact, I should ask for something
non-caffeinated from now on.
This lady is funny.
What are you doing?
Anya, are you all right?
Did you burn yourself?
It got on my clothes a little.
What a careless child.
If Twilight had trained her properly,
she would have caught that cup
before it fell down.
He's obviously too busy
to be training her.
Hey Bond, don't you dare lick it.
It's poisonous to you.
In that case,
it's the wife's duty
to strictly raise the child.
It's impossible for this woman
since she can't even scold her child.
Let me take over. If I become the mother,
I'll set a minute-by-minute schedule,
and train her both
mentally and physically.
Give me a month and I'll turn her into
a Stella Star producing machine.
Anya firmly rejects this mother!
Hot chocolate is very nice
because it's so nutritious.
TWILIGHT, I SUGGEST YOU FIND SOMEONE NEW
TO PLAY THE ROLE OF YOUR WIFE
I don't know why, but Anya wants to
cling onto Mother right now.
Why all of a sudden?
Mother, I love you the most in the world
because you wipe up spilled hot chocolate.
Anya!
What kind of reason is that?
I can spoil her too.
By the way Anya,
I'll give you a really delicious
imported hot chocolate next time.
Hiss!
Why?
She might be feeling nervous
because it's her first time meeting you.
Anya, go play with Bond over there.
I have Father and Mother who are close,
and I have Bond.
Anya is so glad that she's the daughter
of the Forger household.
I'm so glad! Seriously.
Loid, I will work hard!
I will do my best for the two of you.
I will wipe hot chocolate forever.
So please…
Huh…
You should be training her not to
spill the drink. Let me take over.
Yor, you're already working hard enough.
That's why Anya is so attached to you.
You don't have to worry about
doing anything more.
Loid…
-I will do my best!
-Like I said, you already are.
A fake smile.
Listen, Nightfall.
A spy must never show his true feelings.
Yes, sir.
Suppress your emotions.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes, sir.
From now on,
I will maintain a poker face forever.
That's going too far…
Lionel of the Defense Force,
Lawrence, the black-market dealer.
Robert, the politician's secretary.
I've studied Twilight in many disguises,
and that's why I know…
His impeccable fake smile…
is tinted with a hint of genuine emotion.
Oh, I remembered that I forgot
to buy potatoes.
I'll be going now.
You should stay until it stops raining.
I'll be off.
She left.
She didn't have an umbrella, right?
I'll walk her to the station.
All right, thank you. Be careful.
Hey, Fiona!
Here's an umbrella.
I forgot to tell you one thing.
Handler told me to partner
with you on your next mission.
Hey, you should've mentioned
something that important earlier…
Nightfall…
I'm glad it's raining today.
You…
I will hide these feelings from him…
I'll inform you of the details
at the hospital.
Because we are spies.
Because the person that I love
taught me to do that.
Until the day the cold war ends…
But…
Sir…
Even just playing
the role of your wife is enough.
I just want to be by your side.
You're losing your edge right now,
while playing house.
During the next mission, I'll show you
how capable I am, and I'll prove…
Please don't cause me any trouble.
I'll prove to you that I'm the only one
who's suited to be your wife.
MISSION 21: JEALOUSY FOR THE FIRST TIME
March on, Bear Squad
of the Army Surveyors!
-Anya, brush your teeth and go to bed.
-Okay.
Captain, surveying on enemy land
is dangerous.
This white bear looks like you, Bond.
Peggy has been shot!
Leave me behind and go on without me.
I'm trusting you to complete
the map for peace…
Penguin!
Hey, I told you to go to sleep.
What's with this gloomy anime?
Penguin…
I'm going to sleep tonight with Penguin.
Do as you like.
Good night.
No!
What happened?
Penguin is dead!
Agent Penguin,
who did this to you?
These are bite marks and claw marks.
It's Penguin's fault.
He took Anya away from me.
It was Bond after all.
-Bond!
-Hey, stop it!
I hate you, Bond!
It's all right, Anya.
I'll sew him up and he'll be fixed.
You can bring Penguin back to life?
Oh no! For some reason, his neck fell off.
He died even more!
I'm so sorry!
Calm down. I'll buy you a new one.
I don't want that.
This penguin is special to Anya.
Because I got it from you, Father!
I understand. I'll fix it up.
So go eat and do your homework.
It's all fixed, Anya.
It kind of looks like Frankenstein.
That can't be helped.
Scars are like medals for a soldier.
Agent Penguin fought to protect peace,
and these injuries are a badge of honor.
A medal?
That's right.
Those scars are nothing to be ashamed of.
Evil Bond! What are you doing here?
Peanuts?
Is he apologizing to Anya?
I think he wants your forgiveness.
What are you going to do?
Remember what Bondman said?
"Yesterday's enemy is today's friend."
The quote from episode 18.
I was injured very badly.
But as for this war,
I will end it,
for the sake of the peanuts. And…
Anya is sorry for saying, "I hate you."
This seals the peace treaty.
If only things were this easy
between East and West.
MISSION 22: UNDERGROUND TENNIS
TOURNAMENT CAMPBELLDON
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita